https://www.ferrum.edu/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentPrivacy PolicyHome/Privacy Policy Privacy Policydryates2020-02-19T18:55:06+00:00 Related PagesAbout Ferrum CollegeOffice of the PresidentRecognitions & AccoladesFerrum College AffiliationsFerrum MagazineFerrum HistoryTimeline of PresidentsVisit Ferrum CollegeDirections to CampusCampus MapPrivacy PolicyFerrum College is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our website. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website.Information We CollectYou provide information to Ferrum College when you fill out online forms on our websites or use a login-required service. Depending on the type of the service, we use your information in different ways as outlined below.INQUIRY AND APPLICATION FORMSYour contact information is used to contact you by phone and/or email in order to provide you with relevant information about the college. If you do not wish to provide your contact information online, you may contact Office of Admissions and request that information be sent through the mail.PURCHASING MERCHANDISE OR DONATING TO THE COLLEGEYour contact information is used to send merchandise to you, and to contact you if necessary.Your financial information is used for billing.If you do not wish to provide your contact or financial information online, you may contact: Office of Institutional Advancement Ferrum College Campus StoreLOGIN SITES AND SERVICESVarious websites and web services of Ferrum College require users to log in to gain access to information and tools reserved for students, faculty, and staff.Creation of a login account requires you to provide your student or faculty/staff email, along with the account password you created for your email account.Our college websites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control.Your PrivacyFerrum College does not sell, rent, or share your personal information with any outside organizations. Ferrum College will abide by all applicable laws governing the release of personal information.Collective information about site users—but never individuals’ information—is used in marketing, advertising and other relationships with third parties.HOW WE USE THIS INFORMATION Ferrum College uses information collected automatically to better understand the needs of website visitors so that we may improve our websites and services.Cookies and User DataWe collect limited, non-personal identifying information your browser makes available when visiting websites. This information—which helps us assess the effectiveness of our websites—includes:Your Internet Protocol address (I.P. address)The Browser type (Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.)Your computer’s operating system (Windows, Macintosh, etc.)Your Internet Service Provider (ISP) (I.E.: AOL, Earthlink, etc.)URLs of the websites you come to our websites fromThe pages on our website that you visitYour country, territory, or regionIn some instances, our websites use cookies that uniquely identify your browser so that we may provide content most relevant to your needs.Data collected using the following services:ANALYTICS Ferrum College utilizes Google AnalyticsCONTACTING THE USER Constant ContactOpt-Out or Change Your Contact InformationOur site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. You may also update your information previously provided to us through another online form.HOW TO UPDATE YOUR INFORMATIONProspective Students: Contact Office of AdmissionsCurrent Students: Contact Office of the RegistrarAlumni: Contact Office of Alumni & Family Programs or Update your informationCurrent Employees: Contact Human Resources or (540) 365-4596.
Main Administration BuildingJohn Wesley Hall 215 Ferrum Mountain Road Ferrum, Virginia 24088Mailing AddressP.O. Box 1000 Ferrum, Virginia 24088 Toggle Sliding Bar AreaWEBSITE SUPPORTSTAFF LOGIN
For the latest information regarding COVID-19, please click here.
